eurorailways.com 2009-11-24

# Euro Railways Privacy Policy Information

|  **Product Families**  
---  

**Useful Information**  

**Euro Railways**  

### Privacy Policy

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact [ _marketing@eurorailways.com_](mailto:marketing@eurorailways.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

This policy covers how **Euro Railways, Inc.** collects and treats information received via its web site. Such information may include information like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and other personal indicia.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that **Euro Railways** does not own or control, or to people that **Euro Railways** does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Euro Railways associated companies such as **WCT** (hotel bookings) ave their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on the links.

#### Information Collection and Use

**Euro Railways** will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. **Euro Railways** collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's machine containing information about the user. By having our site set a cookie the user would not have to enter their personal information more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site; for example, the user will not receive personalized service. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log files capture the cookie ID and IP address but are not linked in the web traffic analysis.

#### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship product orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for products, and an outside company to provide on-line financing application and approval for some of our products. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We partner with other parties to provide specific web related services. When the user uses these services on our web site, we will only share names, or other information that is necessary for the third party to provide the service. Services include online surveys, search, dealer locators, “contact us” or “personal travel assistant” forms. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing the requested services.

#### Links

Euro Railways web site contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Euro Railways is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

#### Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested includes user information (email address, such as visitor or customer type, reason for purchase) and demographic information (zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, and better understanding customer demographics.

#### Security

This web site takes stringent precautions to protect our users' information.  When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with encryption software, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also have stringent protection policies for protecting user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email to [ _marketing@eurorailways.com._](mailto:marketing@eurorailways.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)

#### Newsletter and Special Offers

We send users who register at **Euro Railways** site or register their products a welcoming email to confirm their registration. Registered customers may elect to receive information on products, services, announcements and special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will prominently post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email or by a prominent notice on the web site. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
